Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Ledger 5446
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Ledger
1883-1969
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (BRT)
5446
15.83 cubic feet
15.8 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Directories, constitutions, manuals, correspondence minutes and other miscellaneous additions to the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Ledger
5649177
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 14, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 13, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5021: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Additional Records 5102: Emergency Board No. 129, Long Island Railroad and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Locals 517 and 1090, Records 5149: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Records 5149 MB: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Memorabilia 5149 P: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Photographs 5348: W.P. Kennedy as President of the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen against the Long Island Railroad Company Court Documents 5612: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Moosic Tunnel Lodge no.93 Meeting Minutes 5623: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Legislative Board of New York Files 5631: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad General Committee File 5647: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Joppa Lodge (Toledo, OH) Minute Books 5894: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Additional Railroad Booklets 6268 P: Joint Committee of Adjustment for the Rock Island System's Order of Railway Conductors and Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Photograph 6312 P: Judith Sullivan Kowalczyk Collection of Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Photographs 6312 PUBS: Judith Sullivan Kowalczyk Collection of Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Publications 6312m: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Annual Report of the Legislative Board 6405 PUBS: William Sharp Collection of The Railroad Trainmen's Journal 6480 MB: Paul Berger Collection of Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Memorabilia
Railroads -- United States.; Railroads -- Employees -- United States; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen; Brotherhood of Railroad Brakemen
5649177
- Spirin, Al, General Chairman, Local 598. Includes minutes and reports, 1923-1969 (Box 190, Folder 1)
- Railroad Retirement Board District Manager, 1940-1949 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  1940's
- Atlantic Coast Line Railroad (Box 191, Folder 2)
- 3030-P General (Box 191, Folder 3)
- Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe (Box 191, Folder 4)
- Baltimore and Ohio (Box 191, Folder 5)
- Bangor and Aroostook (Box 191, Folder 6)
- Bessemer and Lake Erie (Box 191, Folder 7)
- Boston and Albany (Box 191, Folder 8)
- Boston and Maine (Box 191, Folder 9)
- Butte, Anaconda and Pacific (Box 191, Folder 10)
- Hours of Service Act (Box 191, Folder 11)
- Power Train Brake Law of 1958 (Box 191, Folder 12)
- Safety Appliances Act (Box 191, Folder 13)
- RRR Act (Box 191, Folder 14)
- Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act (Box 191, Folder 15)
- Railway Labor Act (Box 191, Folder 16)
- Transportation Act of 1958 (Box 191, Folder 17)
- U.S. Court Decisions (Box 191, Folder 18)
- 4300-1-NL (Bus and Track) General (Box 191, Folder 19)
- Petition of E. Brooke Matlack, Incorporated (Box 191, Folder 20)
- Roadway Express Incorporated (Box 191, Folder 21)
- New York City Transport Company (Box 191, Folder 22)
- Yellow Coach Lines (Box 191, Folder 23)
- Interstate Motor Lines (Box 191, Folder 24)
- Federal Employees Liability Act (Box 191, Folder 25)
- Full Crew (Canadian) (Box 191, Folder 26)
- Union Railway Company (Box 191, Folder 27)
- Great Lakes - Ohio River (Box 191, Folder 28)
- Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad FD 13737 (Box 192, Folder 1)
- C&NWRR FD 13172 (Box 192, Folder 2)
- C&NW FD 13907 (Box 192, Folder 3)
- P CB&Q F016395 (Box 192, Folder 4)
- Chicago, Burlington and Quincy FD 14161 (Box 192, Folder 5)
- CRO&P FD 17060 (Box 192, Folder 6)
- Louisiana - Proposed Consolidation of Railroad Passenger Terminal Facilities at New Orleans (Box 192, Folder 7)
- Illinois Central - Wages, 1900 (Box 193, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous NRAB, 1940-1955 (Box 193, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous United States Department of Labor, Financial Reports, 1963 (Box 193, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous United States Department of Transportation, 1968 (Box 193, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous correspondence re agreements, 1932-1966 (Box 193, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Minutes of Joint General Committee, ORC&B, BRT, AT&SF, Coast Lines, 1914 (Box 193, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Memo to Grievance Committee Bus Department, 1961 (Box 193, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Mediation Agreements, 1939-1955 (Box 193, Folder 8)
- Improved Wages, 1966; CU Terminal, 1968; Inter-Union Correspondence, 1939-1968 (Box 193, Folder 9)
- Union Belt Railroad Yardmasters, 1945 (Box 193, Folder 10)
- Unification Proposal, 1965 (Box 193, Folder 11)
- Canadian W/Rs 14500-N (Box 193, Folder 12)
- CNRR W 1961 W-R Movement, 1962, 1961-1962 (Box 193, Folder 13)
- CN Ry-W 1961 W-R Movement (Box 193, Folder 14)
- Lawsuit, BRT & SUNA (Box 193, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous (Box 193, Folder 16)
- New York City Case - Whitney (Box 193, Folder 17)
- Propaganda (Box 193, Folder 18)
- Q.B. McLay (Box 193, Folder 19)
- Whitney (Box 193, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence re BRT.SUNA Jurisdiction of C.U.T. (Box 194, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous NMB Certification BRT, 1962 (Box 194, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Propaganda Files (Box 194, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous BRT 1910-11, 1910-1911 (Box 194, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous BRT/SUNA 1930's, 1930-1939 (Box 194, Folder 5)
- C-N, 1950-1969 (Box 195, Folder 1)
  filed alphabetically by Railroad, includes correspondence
- Ohio-River Terminal Case (Box 196, Folder 1)
- Washington Job Protection Agreement (Box 196, Folder 2)
- King versus United States (Texas and New Orleans) (Box 196, Folder 3)
- NY, NH, and HRR Old Colony (Box 196, Folder 4)
- Minnesota- Reports on Reorganization of Minnesota Legislation Boards and Quarterly Reports, 1932-1942 (Box 196, Folder 5)
- Volumes on Crew Consist and Full Crew (Box 196, Folder 6)
- Schedule booklets, manuals, reports, rules, rituals (Box 197, Folder 1)
- Directory 1968, Programs, "Main Street, not Wall Street," BRT Anti-SUNA Emblems, Anti-Whitney letters, Insurance booklets, RLEA voting record, 1966, manuals, 1966-1968 (Box 198, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Publications (Box 199, Folder 1)
- "BRT Topics," Miscellaneous Transcripts, Southern California Rapid Transit District Publications, Road Train and Engine Service Assignments, Special Adjustment Board #18, Trainmen's Settlements, "BRT Floodlight," Reports, Roster, Insurance Department Publ (Box 200, Folder 1)
- Directories, Miscellaneous, "Dispensations - BRT" (board volume) (Box 201, Folder 1)
- Duplicate copies of "Circular of Instructions" and Constitutions (Box 202, Folder 1)
- Duplicate copies of "Circular of Instructions" and Constitutions, miscellaneous V.E.S. (Box 203, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Additional Publications (Local 615 minute book; Canada pension plan); local 834 Report 1931; Miscellaneous Correspondence; Local 262, Mobridge, South Dakota, 1903-1920, Board Volume - Scrapbook; 70th anniversary booklet BR5 1833-1958; 75th A, 1883-1920 (Box 205, Folder 1)
- Subordinate Lodge - Charter Members by Lodge (Box 206, Folder 4)
- Subordinate Lodge - Charter Members by Lodge (Box 206, Folder 3)
- Subordinate Lodge - Charter Members by Lodge (Box 206, Folder 2)
- Subordinate Lodge - Charter Members by Lodge (Box 206, Folder 1)